<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Wenbo Lv</title>
    <link>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Wenbo Lv</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>arcR</title>
      <link>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/arcr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/arcr/</guid>
      <description>goal The goal of arcR is to integrate the benefits of R and ArcGIS with using ArcGIS in R.&#xA;document You can see the document of arcR in here&#xA;source code The source code of arcR is in here&#xA;feedback If you have any questions or suggestions, please post them in arcR github repo issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>esp</title>
      <link>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/esp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/esp/</guid>
      <description>goal Assessing the spatial association between variables through an equivalent geographical detector q-statistic within a regression framework.&#xA;document You can see the document of esp in here&#xA;source code The source code of esp is in here&#xA;feedback If you have any questions or suggestions, please post them in esp github repo issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>gdverse</title>
      <link>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/gdverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/gdverse/</guid>
      <description>goal The goal of gdverse is to support the geodetector model and its variants.&#xA;document You can see the document of gdverse in here&#xA;source code The source code of gdverse is in here&#xA;feedback If you have any questions or suggestions, please post them in gdverse github repo issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>geocn</title>
      <link>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/geocn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/geocn/</guid>
      <description>goal The goal of geocn is to provide various commonly used spatial data related to Chinese regions in the R programming environment.&#xA;document You can see the document of geocn in here&#xA;source code The source code of geocn is in here&#xA;feedback If you have any questions or suggestions, please post them in geocn github repo issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>geocomplexity</title>
      <link>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/geocomplexity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/geocomplexity/</guid>
      <description>goal The goal of geocomplexity is to support geocomplexity computation and applications.&#xA;document You can see the document of geocomplexity in here&#xA;source code The source code of geocomplexity is in here&#xA;feedback If you have any questions or suggestions, please post them in geocomplexity github repo issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>geosom</title>
      <link>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/geosom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/geosom/</guid>
      <description>goal The goal of geosom is to achieve Spatially-Aware Self-Organizing Maps(GeoSOM) Model in R.&#xA;document You can see the document of geosom in here&#xA;source code The source code of geosom is in here&#xA;feedback If you have any questions or suggestions, please post them in geosom github repo issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sdsfun</title>
      <link>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/sdsfun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/sdsfun/</guid>
      <description>goal The goal of sdsfun is to provide miscellaneous functions that summarize common operations of R packages (such as sf and terra packages) related to spatial data science.&#xA;document You can see the document of sdsfun in here&#xA;source code The source code of sdsfun is in here&#xA;feedback If you have any questions or suggestions, please post them in sdsfun github repo issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>spatbox</title>
      <link>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/spatbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/spatbox/</guid>
      <description>source code The source code of spatbox is in here&#xA;feedback If you have any questions or suggestions, please post them in spatbox github repo issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>spEcula</title>
      <link>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/specula/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/specula/</guid>
      <description>goal The goal of spEcula is to make it easier to use R for spatial prediction based on various spatial relationships (e.g. spatial dependence, spatial heterogeneity and geographical similarity).&#xA;document You can see the document of spEcula in here&#xA;source code The source code of spEcula is in here&#xA;feedback If you have any questions or suggestions, please post them in spEcula github repo issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tidyrgeoda</title>
      <link>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/tidyrgeoda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spatlyu.github.io/projects/tidyrgeoda/</guid>
      <description>goal The goal of tidyrgeoda is to provide an interface for rgeoda to integrate with sf objects and the tidyverse.&#xA;document You can see the document of tidyrgeoda in here&#xA;source code The source code of tidyrgeoda is in here&#xA;feedback If you have any questions or suggestions, please post them in tidyrgeoda github repo issue.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
